<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yawar Mohammad Khan</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Yawar Mohammad Khan</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Personal blog &amp; website using Hugo</title><link>/posts/hugo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/hugo/</guid><description>&lt;p>For some time now, I’ve been considering starting a blog to share my thoughts and projects with the world. Initially, my personal website was a simple online CV, built with plain HTML and Bootstrap, and hosted on AWS S3.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After exploring my options, I began searching for a suitable static site generator that would allow me to publish blog posts using markdown. This approach seemed perfect since I was already familiar with markdown. This search led me to &lt;a href="https://jekyllrb.com/" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Jekyll&lt;/a>. The learning curve with Jekyll was minimal, and setting up the website on GitHub Pages was straightforward. However, I eventually got caught up in other projects and life, and never managed to complete the blog.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Welcome to my personal website, where I plan to share stories, thoughts, lessons, and experiments from my professional and personal experiences.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am a seasoned &lt;strong>engineering leader&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>software engineer&lt;/strong> with a passion for solving complex problems. My expertise lies in the domain of data engineering &amp;amp; massively distributed systems.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Apart from technology, my other interests are &lt;em>art&lt;/em>, &lt;em>photography&lt;/em> and &lt;em>motorsports (F1)&lt;/em>.&lt;/p>
&lt;div>
&lt;img src="./images/lines.svg" id="hp">
&lt;/div>
&lt;br/>
&lt;br/>
&lt;br/>
&lt;hr/>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Disclaimer: Posts on this blog are my own views, not my employer’s.&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>